codecondo.com 2015-06-21

# Privacy Policy - CodeCondo

This Privacy Policy is part of CodeCondo’s Terms of Service and covers the usage of reader’s information, including Personally Information and also the information obtained when you access or log in to CodeCondo, and/or register for content provided by CodeCondo.  
By visiting CodeCondo, viewing our content or research or using any of our services, you acknowledge that you accept the policies and practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

At CodeCondo, we understand that privacy of your personal information is important. Below is the list of information we collect and receive when you use and visit our website. We won’t sell any of your personal information to third parties. Don’t worry you information is safe with us.

**Information we collect  
**  
We may collect below information of yours regarding your computer or device which include Personally Identifiable Information

Name, Email-address, Activities or Content Viewed on CodeCondo

**We use your information  
**  
To enhance our website  
(we try continuously to improve our website contribution based on the feedback and information you give us)  
To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to respond more effectively to your customer service requests and support needs)  
To customize your experience  
(It helps us to come back with best to your individual needs)  
To send periodic emails  
To process transactions  
To administer a promotion, survey, contest or other website feature

**Do we use cookies?  
**  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a website or its service provider transfers to your computer’s via your Web browser (if you allow) which permits the websites or service providers systems to identify your web browser and remember and record information.

We use cookies to perceive and save your likings whenever you visit our website again, tracking advertisements and compile mass data about site interaction and website traffic so that we can offer better website tools and experience in the future.

**Do we share your information to third parties?  
**  
We do not trade or sell your personal information to anyone. This doesn’t involve trusted third parties who help us in, conducting our business, operating our website or servicing you, as long as those parties agree to keep this information private. We may also provide your information if we believe that it is worthfull and is fitting in law, protect others or ours right, safety. However, information which is non-personally identifiable may be provided to other parties for advertising and marketing purpose.

**Third party links**

Sometimes, at our diplomacy, we may include or provide third party products or services on our site. These third party websites have independent privacy policies. We therefore have no accountability or control for the activities and contents of these linked websites. Nevertheless, we work towards safeguarding the integrity of our website and welcome any feedback about these websites.

**Adsense policy**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on CodeCondo. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users, based on their visit to CodeCondo and other websites on the Internet. You can have a brief look on Google’s Adsense policy [here](https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/48182)

**Your Agreement**

By using our website, you agree to our website’s privacy policy.

**Any Changes to our Privacy Policy**

Any improvement in our Privacy Policy will be updated in this page.
